#### [How do we support you streaming project...](https://www.tunedglobal.com/services-to-build-streaming-app?hsLang=en)
    
    #### [How do we support you streaming project...](https://www.tunedglobal.com/services-to-build-streaming-app?hsLang=en)
    
    * [
        
        ##### Branded app
        
        Our white label streaming service if you need a front-end and backend ready-to-go.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/white-label-music?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/white-label-music?hsLang=en)[Branded app](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/white-label-music?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### Music-as-a-Service
        
        Music catalog ingestion & delivery including metadata, assets and rights management.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/content-delivery?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/content-delivery?hsLang=en)[Music-as-a-Service](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/content-delivery?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### Streaming service APIs
        
        A set of documented APIs to help you implement streaming features in your existing platform.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-api?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-api?hsLang=en)[Streaming service APIs](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-api?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### Playlisting tool
        
        Music Curation solution to easily create playlists that comply with your licensing agreements.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/playlisting-tool-for-business?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/playlisting-tool-for-business?hsLang=en)[Playlisting tool](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/playlisting-tool-for-business?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### AutomixIQ
        
        SDK that enhances music streaming experiences with seamless song transitions, akin to a DJ mix](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/pacemaker-autmixiq-music-ai-dj?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/pacemaker-autmixiq-music-ai-dj?hsLang=en)[AutomixIQ](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/pacemaker-autmixiq-music-ai-dj?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### Licensing
        
        A consultancy service to help you navigate the complex music licensing space.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-licensing?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-licensing?hsLang=en)[Licensing](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-licensing?hsLang=en)
        
    * [
        
        ##### Social Radio
        
        SDK that adds a social experience to music apps with live broadcasting and real-time interaction.](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/social-radio-music-audio-app?hsLang=en)
        
        ##### [](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/social-radio-music-audio-app?hsLang=en)[Social Radio](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/social-radio-music-audio-app?hsLang=en)

    #### Features
    
    #### Features

     [.png?width=26&height=26&name=interview%20(1).png) Request a demo](https://www.tunedglobal.com/contact?hsLang=en)

    #### Overview
    
    #### Overview
    
    What makes us different in the B2B music tech market is our innovative backend technology for streaming services. Our next generation cloud based infrastructure allow streaming services to scale on-demand and we can ingest millions of tracks in a matter of time without performance issues.

    #### In deep
    
    #### In deep

    #### About
    
    #### About
    
    We are your 360º B2B music streaming technology partner that helps to quickly launch and grow streaming services around the world. The company develops simple, fast and engaging music, audio and video streaming platforms for enterprises and start-ups.

    #### [News & Press](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/news?hsLang=en)
    
    #### [News & Press](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/news?hsLang=en)

    [Tuned Global offers a new Social Radio experience — turning listeners into creators](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/news/social-radio-add-social-features-for-music-apps?hsLang=en)

* RESOURCES
    
    #### [VLOG - Stream by Stream](https://www.tunedglobal.com/stream-by-stream?hsLang=en)
    
    #### [VLOG - Stream by Stream](https://www.tunedglobal.com/stream-by-stream?hsLang=en)
    
    #### We interview music tech expert to help you in your streaming journey
    
    * [
        
        Sylvain Delange explains what labels expect from new local DSPs](https://www.tunedglobal.com/stream-by-stream?hsLang=en#sylvain-believe-labels)
    * [
        
        The process of Music Licensing and Publishing with Keith Bernstein](https://www.tunedglobal.com/stream-by-stream?hsLang=en#Keith-crunchdigital-publishing)
    * [
        
        Jean-Luc Biaulet demystifies the role of enriched metadata for the industry](https://www.tunedglobal.com/stream-by-stream?hsLang=en#jeanluc-musicstory-metadata)

    #### [BLOG - #Power of music](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/?hsLang=en)
    
    #### [BLOG - #Power of music](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/?hsLang=en)
    
    #### Our blog where we share our views about trends in music and streaming tech

    [The Transformative Power of Music Therapy in Health & Wellness](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/music-as-transformative-power-in-healthcare?hsLang=en)

    [Microstreaming: How brands use niche music streaming to reach key audiences](https://blog.tunedglobal.com/microstreaming-how-brands-use-niche-music-streaming-to-reach-key-audiences?hsLang=en)

Privacy Policy Statement for Tuned Global
-----------------------------------------

In relation to this document, the terms 'we', 'our' and 'us' means Tuned Global Pty Ltd. 'The website' means the website from where you linked to this document.  
  
**Our commitment to your privacy**  
We will not sell, trade, give or rent any personally identifiable information obtained from you to a third party unless you consent.  
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
  
**Information gathered and how it is used**  
The kinds of personal information we collect will depend on the purpose(s) for which we're collecting it, but may include the following:

* Your name.
* Your contact details, such as an email address.
* Your entertainment preferences (for example, the music or artists you like).
* The details of any specific goods or services you've browsed, purchased or requested.

You can always refuse to give Tuned Global any of the personal information we request, but that may mean we can't provide you with some or all of the goods or services you require. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalise your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To send periodic emails

We generally collect personal information directly from the individual concerned.  
We may collect personal information about you from a social media platform when you use it to register or login at any of the Tuned Global websites, but you will be given the opportunity to authorise this at the time you register. For example, if you use your Facebook profile to register with a Tuned Global website, you will be asked to confirm that you are happy to share information from your profile with Tuned Global. Where you give Tuned Global access to one of your social media profiles in this way, we will only collect information that you have made publicly available, including:

* your name;
* your email address;
* your location;
* your gender;
* your date of birth; and
* your "likes", "shares" and public posts.

Credit Card information is NOT stored:  
Credit Card information is not stored on Tuned Global servers; all credit card information is stored by our payment gateway providers in a PCI compliant environment. This information is not available to Tuned Global personnel.  
  
Email messaging  
You can nominate the information you receive via email, if any:  
We only send our e-mail newsletters to users who ask to receive them through our subscription form or request more information about us. Once you are on the list - you can easily get off. Simply select the link at the bottom of all emails to halt any further communication (other than receipts and financial information). If you change or move e-mail addresses please update your details on the website to ensure you receive the information you have requested.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to keep track of advertisements.  
  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
  
**Accessing and correcting your personal information**  
Under the Privacy Act, you generally have a right to seek access to personal information that Tuned Global holds about you. You also generally have a right to ask Tuned Global to correct personal information about you that you think is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading.  
If you wish to seek access to the personal information Tuned Global holds about you, please make a request in writing to our Privacy Officer (contact details are set out at the end of this policy). Your request should state whether you are seeking access to all the personal information Tuned Global holds about you or to particular personal information (in which case you should specify that in your request). You should also provide some form of identification (e.g. a photocopy of your driver’s licence or passport) so Tuned Global can verify that you are the person to whom the personal information relates. You should also include details of how Tuned Global can contact you in case we need to discuss your request. If you need more information before making a formal request for access, please contact the Privacy Officer, who can explain how Tuned Global will handle your access request and assist you in making that request.  
Tuned Global will assume (unless you tell us otherwise) that your request relates to Tuned Global’s current records about you. These current records will include personal information about you which is included in our databases and in paper files, and which may be used by Tuned Global on a day to day basis. To provide you with access to current personal information, Tuned Global will ordinarily provide you with a print-out of the relevant personal information from its databases, or with photocopies of records which are held only on paper files.  
If you think that any of the personal information Tuned Global holds about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please provide our Privacy Officer with a written request for correction (contact details are set out at the end of the policy). It is Tuned Global’s policy to consider and respond to any requests for correction within 30 days of receiving the request.  
If Tuned Global agrees that your personal information is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, Tuned Global will correct it for you. If we do not agree with your view, we will provide you with reasons for our view, and will provide you with an opportunity to make a statement of your view and have it included with the information.  
  
**How to make a complaint?**  
If you believe that we have breached this policy, or any of the Australian Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act, then you should make a complaint to Tuned Global in the first instance. You should address your complaint in writing to our Privacy Officer (contact details are set out below), and you should include as much detail as you can about the personal information affected, and the circumstances that you believe amount to a breach of this policy or the APPs.  
We will generally provide a written response to your complaint within 30 days.

If you are unhappy with our response to your complaint, you have the right to make a complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner. Details of how to contact the OAIC are provided on its website at [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/).

**Contacting Tuned Global**  
If you have any questions about Tuned Global's handling of personal information, or if you wish to make an access or correction request or complaint, you should contact the Tuned Global Privacy Officer by one of the following methods:  
By email: [info@tunedglobal.com](mailto:info@tunedglobal.com)[](mailto:info@tunedglobal.com)By post: Tuned Global - Suite 6 Level 1/425 Docklands Dr, Docklands VIC 3008, Australia

**Your consent**  
By using our sites, you consent to our website’s privacy policy and to us collecting and using this information.  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.  
  
**Copyright**  
All information on this website is copyright and may not be copied without prior written consent from the copyright owner.  
  
**Disclaimer**  
All information on this website is provided as-is and without any guarantee. You accept full responsibility for any consequences of use or misuse of any information provided on this website.  
  
You can find more information about privacy and the protection of your personal information on the website of the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at [www.oaic.gov.au.](http://www.oaic.gov.au./)

#### Tuned global

* [HOME - B2B Music Streaming Technology to build streaming apps](https://www.tunedglobal.com/)
* [BRANDED APP - White label streaming service for music, audio and video](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/white-label-music)
* [AUTOMIXIQ - Seamless song transitions for a professional DJ-like experience](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/pacemaker-autmixiq-music-ai-dj)
* [SOCIAL RADIO - Add live broadcasting and interaction to your music app](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/social-radio-music-audio-app)
* [CONTENT - Music content catalogue delivery, ingestion and metadata](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/content-delivery)
* [LICENSING - Music licensing consultancy for streaming services](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-services/music-licensing)
* [TECHNOLOGY - streaming backend infrastructure with AI recommendation engine](https://www.tunedglobal.com/streaming-technology)
* [CLIENTS - Companies using Tuned Global as a steaming technology provider](https://www.tunedglobal.com/tuned-global-white-label-music-solutions-case-studies)

#### Contact

Australia

United Kingdom

USA

### Subscribe to our Newsletter

Copyright © 2020 Tuned Global. Read our [Privacy Policy](https://www.tunedglobal.com/privacy-policy-statement-tuned-global) or [Contact Us](https://www.tunedglobal.com/contact?hsLang=en)
